Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was hurt during the
production of this show.
Erlik Khan!
You made me...
talk to your soul.
- Talks in Mongol -
What have souls told you...
about Noyan?
You shall not mention...
the holy name of my father!
Everybody in Sogut is talking about your
victory, Togay.
Only an idiot prides on his victory.
The greater the victory is,
the greater the pain is.
What do you want, Petrus?
To distroy Osman's dignity which
has taken damage.
It has been done.
Now it's time to shed blood.
I thought you wanted brother blood.
My father Noyan told me to get faster
to drink Osman's blood.
Why?
My father told me Osman
is a Gokboru.
Wolves...
went through Khan Tengri Mountain.
There are four classes of wolves.
Grey-maned wolf destroys all the herd when
he attacks.
But eats only one of them.
They are relentless.
Maned wolves destroys half of the
herd when he attacks.
Eats only one of them.
They have a moral code sometimes.
Bozkurt...
destroys only one in a herd...
eats half of it...
takes the other half to his herd.
Bozkurts have manners.
What about Gokboru?
Gokboru... Gokboru...
The wolf with sky-like feathers
The wolf that Oguz Khan mentioned,
that lives once in a thousand years.
When that wolf joins the herd, he makes
the herd stronger, thougher.
The shamans which connects me
to my father...
told me that Osman is a Gokboru.
Osman will attack my herd only for me.
Only for me.
That's why I have to move first.
I am here to offer you something
that can make your herd stronger.
- Who?
- Inegol's Lord Nicola.
My Bala! We should do our best.
We should make her better.
Inshallah, my Bey.
You can mind your own business.
She is here because she accepted
our invitation.
She is entrusted to us.
I surely will be taking good care of her.
It's not so deep, thank Allah.
I have no time to lose for
a little wound.
He wounded my father, killed
my Alps.
I'll find Togay and kill him!
You may not be as lucky as
this next time.
Sorry to hear what happened.
I'm sorry to hear what happened,
Malhun Hatun.
I heard you were wounded...
you have been brought to the tent...
in the arms of Osman Bey.
Apparently, our Osman Bey values you
very much.
What was he supposed to do, Hazal Hatun?
Should his Alps have carried me? Come on.
He respects my father Umur Bey.
Of course, of course he does.
He carried you himself because
he respects your father Umur Bey.
My Bey, Savcı Bey and Lena Hatun took off
with their Alps.
What about the guest Beys?
They are returning to their tents under
our Alps' security.
What di that infidel do, Osman Bey?
Togay, Bamsı Bey, Togay.
He attacked Malhun Hatun's alps.
This Togay will cause so much trouble
if we don't make a move.
Let him be, Uncle.
We are going to bother him, no worries.
As long as we are together, he can't
do anything, my Bey.
We bait him with his own bait!
We should also find the betrayer
in us and punish him...
while considering Togay on the other hand.
Nicola will return eventually.
Jackals and pigs will make an alliance.
If we unite, neither jackals nor pigs
can stop us.
This was why Togay attacked the meeting
and tried to kill Beys.
However, we are dealing with so much
things including Togay.
Davut Bey is right. When Nicola returns,
they are going to make an alliance.
But Bamsı Bey is also right.
Jackals and pigs cannot stop us.
Listen to me carefully now. I am
announcing my new goal.
What are you doing?
That's what jackals do.
They are nine.
They walked side by side till here,
They went on in single file.
They must be near.
Let's go.
Hide.
Ambush!
Attack!
Suci.
Cerkutay, my brother!
Don't worry, they lost us.
They can't find us.
You'll live, Cerkutay.
Cerkutay doesn't die.
- I am really happy to see you.
- Sshhh! Silent!
- Aygül Stop!
- Why would you stop me?
Come here.
Let him be alive. He'll take us to
Togay.
What I am saying is that I'll not
come here for a while.
I need to step back.
You proved yourself to Osman already.
What makes you step back?
I am the one whose life is in danger.
Are you afriad of someone whose dignity
is vanishing step by step?
Lord Nicola returned from
Emperor's castle.
So Emperor still trusts him.
He must be stronger now.
Both stronger and more crowded.
To finish Osman, Nicola now sees
Togay.
Osman's enemies have never been
united that well before.
And you have never been closer to
the post, Dündar Bey.
Do you understand that you should
no longer be afraid, Dündar Bey?
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come.
My Bey, Cerkutay and Aygül are back.
They brought a Mongol.
How has Nicola changed?
You'll see yourself now.
He returned from Constantinie with
the strenght you cannot even imagine.
What does he want?
He couldn't accept Flatyos' death.
Do not dare to bother him.
Be ready to die, Aris.
I am always ready to die for the
empire, for you Nicola.
All the Lords are going to be ready for
a final attack.
We'll take Sogut to break Osman.
Do we have soldiers for that, Nicola?
Do you want death now or when
Osman's sword hit you, huh?
I want to die in the battle, Nicola.
Osman gathered the Beys.
He wants Inegol.
Tell me, Aris.
If Osman conquers Inegol, how and where
are you going to live?
You'll be sitting in your castle
like bumblebees.
You wouldn't want that, would you?
I am ready to die for you, Nicola.
Then you should listen to me
real carefully.
While Osman is planning to take Inegol,
we'll hit him in Sogut.
Emperor will send a huge army.
The fearful commander Kolonos will
be leading them.
So the Turks will end finally,
right Nicola?
May Jesus protect our Empire.
Jesus couldn't even protected himself
from Rome!
Dear Helen, finally it's time to meet
Geyhatu's hunter dog Black Shaman Togay.
He departed, sir.
And you Aris, see all the Lords
and tell them to get their armies ready.
Talk, where is Togay?
So that's it, huh?
You are going to talk.
Cerkutay.
Where is Togay?
Talk, where is that ignoble who wounded
my father, killed my alps?
Talk!
Togay is now you shade.
He'll be after you until he kills you.
Malhun Hatun!
I need him alive.
I have to talk to you.
You keep going. If this one dies or
escpaes...
then you'll witness my wrath.
You promised me not to act by yourself.
But you didn't keep your word
and went after Togay!
You left me no choice, Osman Bey.
You tried to hide it even though you knew
it was Togay who attacked.
I was trying to protect you.
The past is past, Osman Bey. We both
want Togay.
We should find out how we
are going to find him.
First of all, we need to
lodge your father.
The right thing is to be together.
If that dog doesn't talk, what is
your plan than?
I'll pour water to scorpion's nest.
He'll come out.
What are you going to give me, Nicola?
The drink I made for Geyhatu
when he came.
Kumis.
To Togay who shot Osman in heart.
Are you showing me respect because you
fear me or...
do you fear Osman?
What I am afraid of is that Osman may
trample your dead body.
Save your anger to Osman, not me.
My anger is enough for both of you.
Shooting him in middle of a meeting
doesn't make you hero, Togay.
My castle, my soldiers, and my spies
will be under your command...
with a single command of mine...
like I did help to Geyhatu.
Will you give your throne to me?
As long as Osman lives, this throne is no
use for neither me nor you, Togay.
In return of the soldiers you'll give me..
I'll let you live in this stone grave.
- Make your mind.
- You'll come back.
You'll come back.
You barbaric.
My brother, help!
You'll live Cerkutay.
You saved my life.
What is wrong with you?
There's something going on since
we captuerd that Mongol.
I remembered my childhood while tracking.
The days I lived in forest.
Is it your childhood or...
the days you fought for Balgay.
Why are you silent?
I was raised by jackals, Aygül.
Jackals are summoning me.
The forest is calling me.
I hear voices they say
"Come to us, Cerkutay"
Are you going to live?
Even if they think I trciked them all...
You should know that I would never
trick Bamsı Bey.
What does that mean?
When moon lights on my sword's steel,
it shines like your eyes.
But...
But?
Cerkutay missed the forest.
Leave then!
How can you go after Togay without
my command?
I am not dead yet, daughter!
You were not in a condition to make call,
my Bey.
How did you allow that?
My beloved daughter goes after that
dirty dog...
and you don't stop her, right?
They are sinless.
They obeyed me.
If Osman Bey didn't hide the fact that he
was after Togay, I wouldn't do this.
I doubt Osman Bey knows what to hide.
Is there anything about Togay?
One of Osman Bey's alps captured their
man, my Bey.
He hasn't talked yet, my Bey.
He'll, he will.
Everyone talks if you know where to hit.
Arrange accomodation for
our Alps to come.
Take care of them. Bring the
rest of the alps to me.
Yes my Bey.
We'll do our job ourselves.
- Alaca Hatun.
- Yes my Bey.
You'll be my eyes and ears.
Don't worry, my Bey. I'll have my eyes
wide open.
I'll be alone with my daughter now.
The one who killed the captive whom Osman
tried to make talk and who told enemies
about the meeting and shed our blood is
the one whose finger fits in this ring.
You did a good job to hide this.
If it's Osman's close ones, Osman may
show mercy.
But if we found him before he does,
we'll make it right.
Is there anything about the owner of
this ring?
Dündar Bey.
Dündar Bey, why are you wandering?
You are wearing off the rugs.
They have never been stronger, Hatun.
Osman's enemies have never been stronger.
Damaging him inside and outside, huh?
What do you mean by inside?
When a Hatun is disturbed by someone or
something...
her man is the real one who will suffer
the consequences.
That man of hers cannot be happy
until she gets happy.
Malhun Hatun seems to bother Bala Hatun
very much.
I know it like the back of my hand...
that she waited Malhun Hatun to die
in the tent today.
You are mistaken, Hatun.
This is Bala Hatun.
So what?
She is a she.
A Hatun is a Hatun.
You are talking to an expert.
You have plans, apparently.
Good then.
Good, good.
Can I, Umur Bey?
Come Osman Bey.
We have been honored Osman Bey.
You are the guests here.
We have been honored.
Here, Osman Bey.
I hope you don't need anything.
We don't, we have everything.
We have been well hosted,
Eyvallah. (thanks)
Eyvallah (you are welcome.)
We are tired of waiting for your words
about the dog who shed our blood, Osman Bey.
Don't worry.
I'll bring Togay's and his soldiers'
heads to you one by one.
Do you have a plan, Osman Bey?
Of course I do, a plan
that will shed blood.
When, Osman Bey?
We accepted your invitation,
came by here.
We almost died?
When?
We are responsible for what happened.
But don't worry about that.
We don't worry about ourselves, Osman Bey.
We worry about the future of our tribe.
We do not fight for ourselves.
We fight for our community.
You hold your head straight against
Geyhatu, you respect our traditions.
But...
You saw what happened when Malhun Hatun
acted herself.
I do not consent to do things
without notifying me.
- Let me leave
- Your lands...
Your invitation.
But this is my tribe, my people,
Osman Bey.
Malhun Hatun, don't leave your father
alone.
Stay with him.
Bala...
I dozed off.
You got tired, didn't you?
May Allah bless you my Bala.
May Allah bless you.
You hosted our guests very well...
like how we were supposed to do.
I am happy if they are happy.
Oh, my Bala, oh.
We are getting through difficult days.
A Kayı Bey and a Kayı Hatun goes
from one difficulty to another.
My Bala.
Do not think that I am angry at you,
accuse you just because...
I am angry at that time.
My Bala, I want something else from you.
Of course my Bey.
You need to feel them, my Bala.
They accepted our invitation, they
migrated here.
They are waiting for a homeland.
And they are already in the target
of our enemies.
Of course they will suspect.
Of course they will want to
interfere in our things.
My Bala, we are the founder ones.
We are the ones that gather people.
We need to be levelheaded.
We will be patient.
We will put up with them.
And we will get rid of the dark clouds
above Kayı Tribe.
We'll spread our light to everywhere.
My Bala.
My Bala?
Hey, rose.
You are secured in my arms.
Sleep here.
Osman is watching for you.
I am here to pay back.
Be quick.
I knew you were still a Mongol.
Cut it!
It's my duty to call Cerkutay to account..
just like how he tricked me, my Bey.
He tricked us all.
All of us.
We wanted to believe, Osman Bey.
We wanted to believe that he repented,
that he'd continue living like a Turk.
Bamsı Bey, that's why we were deceived.
So that was why infidels knew every
step of ours.
We gave martyrs because of that betrayer,
my Bey!
Did you spot him through?
Are you sure it was Cerkutay?
Bamsı Bey, I wouldn't give his name if
I was not sure.
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come!
Are you sure, Gencebey?
Tell me, Aygül.
Was he suspicious?
I was raised by jackals, Aygül.
The forest is calling for me.
I hear voices they say
"Cerkutay come to us"
Cerkutay missed the forest.
He spoke to me like
taking a farewell.
What did he say, daughter?
They may think that I tricked everyone,
but I would never trick Bamsı Bey, he said.
He really liked you, Bamsı Bey.
Why did he betray?
Why?
The meeting is over.
We'll find and punish him.
My wound is not deep.
I'll come too, my Bey.
I will come too, my Bey.
Can I, my Bey?
Let's go!
You acted like a Mongol, don't be upset.
I finally found home.
Then I betrayed again.
I cannot go back.
Osman Bey would kill me.
It was not your home. Come with me.
To your real home.
Return to Mongols.
Togay will accept a fighter like you.
He'll suspect me.
I'll defend you, tell them you saved me.
Let's go then.
Cerkutay is hungry.
You were always hungry, Cerkutay.
I can't believe how Cerkutay did this
to us.
He made us like him so much.
He was joking around everytime I saw him.
- He was a good friend to Aygül as well.
- True.
She must be devestated.
- Salamun Aleikum
- Aleikum salam.
Alaikum salam.
I am searching for Osman Bey.
He is not in the tent.
Okay.
I'll check that Mongol dog.
Stop, Hatun.
What is it, Bala Hatun?
You tell me, Malhun Hatun.
You are acting by yourself again.
The only one who knows where Togay is
is the dog who you cannot make talk.
Now let me make that dog talk.
The thing you cannot do.
What is it? Is there something wrong?
That dog went off.
What are you talking about Hatun?
Step back while you are looking
dead in my eye!
I'd look at Osman Bey's eyes
if he were here.
You couldn't take care of a dog!
Tell me.
Who is this dog?
How did you got out?
My blood brother Cerkutay saved me
from Osman's cage.
Tell me.
I am Balgay's commander Cerkutay.
Balgay is dead.
Why are you alive?
I didn't give my soul to Erlik Khan to
take revenge from Osman.
- Tell me.
- I obeyed Osman.
I tricked him.
Why now?
Black Shaman Togay is back.
I came back to fight with him.
What do you offer to Togay, Cerkutay?
Geyhatu's two huge enemy will unite.
I know where Umur Bey is setting tents.
If we don't raid them now, they'll
get bigger.
The smell of treason.
The goat smell on you outsmell the
smell of treason!
Why would I believe you?
I didn't sell myself to Osman!
I will save Göktuğ like I did Suci.
Give me a chance, Togay.
Stake him on the arms!
If he lies, cut his tongue!
Cut his head off his body!
Give his body to ravens,
give his soul to Erlik Khan!
Time to shed blood!
Sir, Cerkutay was right. There are tents,
they are just setting up.
Let's go!
Ya Allah!
Allah is eternal!
- Cerkutay!
- Mad girl, what are you doing here?
I thought you'd die!
Cerkutay does not die.
Let's go!
Ertugrul Ghazi's son Gokboru.
Where is your master Togay?
Come here Turk.
My Bey, we killed all of the soldiers.
I left one wounded as you said.
When that soldiers goes back to Togay,
he'll want to come back stronger.
He'll get help from Nicola.
Cerkutay!
You did well, Cerkutay.
Eyvallah my Bey.
I wish I was dead instead of...
saving him, my Bey
They say betrayal is though...
I now know it.
Then you should save your brother,
Cerkutay.
That way, you'll have no debt left.
- Are you fine, my Bey?
- I am fine.
I am fine.
Why did Boke call me Gokboru?
I was thinking about that.
He showed his souls your blood, my Bey.
Gokboru bit us.
We got ambushed.
We shall mount up.
We have no place for weaks.
- Can I come in Umur Bey?
- Come, Osman Bey.
Is there something?
Did you find that soldier you failed
to keep possession of?
Osman Bey, I believe in your good deeds.
I have no doubts.
But, forgive me. I think there are
uncommitted things going on in this tent.
How can a captive can run away?
You are right, Umur bey. Obviously,
someone helped him.
We know it, Osman Bey. It was the Mongol
soldier you took in your tent.
Was that a part of your plan?
Eyvallah Osman Bey.
So, what did you get out of this plan?
We cornered Togay.
- What did you get?
- We killed his soldiers.
- What about Togay?
- He didn't take the bait.
If you notified us, we'd find
and take his head, Osman Bey.
There are two rules in this land.
The careless dies in the path of battle.
And the ones who fights Kayı...
die under our swords.
Everybody will learn that...
they shouldn't be hostile against Kayı.
Both our friends and enemies.
I want to know...
everything about Malhun Hatun.
Your command, my Bey.
He doesn't want to include us.
What will we do?
We'll find out where Togay is.
Then I know what to do.
- Speaks in Greek -
Until all of the Turks die...
We don't need anyone.
Your soldiers do, sir.
The soldiers are anxious.
They think we're like this because you
don't go to church and beg Jesus.
Only a shepherd needs a herd.
I'm the owner of this herd!
The real owner of the herd...
we will lose if you don't beg Jesus.
Your God already left us.
Sir!
Do you want to lose
the war before it begins?
Don't! If you kill the priest, we won't
have anyone to fight with us!
Togay is back.
You did it, sir!
You did it!
I knew he was.
I knew.
Get out.
I said you would come.
I said you would come for Osman.
I'm sorry for your soldiers by the way.
The soldiers' spirits are with me.
I don't know where
the hell are they but...
Osman's breath is behind you.
I proposed you an agreement.
You refused it. So?
Your soldiers are dead.
Then you came back. However, it's
too late.
You refused my proposal.
Tell me now, Togay.
What do yoı have for me?
I'll give you Söğüt.
How?
Petrus dug tunnels under the Söğüt.
So, you harmed Umur Bey via these tunnels.
I knew...
we would deal sooner or later.
May your war be holy, Osman Bey.
You killed Togay's soldiers.
Thank you, brother.
However, I won't feel comfortable
until I kill him.
- You will do it too.
- Inshallah.
However, you didn't tell
us about the trick you played.
The Beys hide some things, brother.
We don't tell everything.
Yes.
You had to believe in Cerkutay's
betrayal so that...
the traitors wouldn't suspect us.
Cerkutay.
So, you deceived us.
My Osman Bey commanded me, so I did it.
How did you believe anyway, my Bey?
Cerkutay, get some rest.
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come in.
Summon Dündar Bey.
It's about something important.
- We have news from Togay.
- Tell me.
- Togay arrived Nikola's castle.
- İnegöl?
Let me go to İnegöl, father.
So that I will ask for Togay.
Nikola is back from Constantine.
The Emperor promised
him support, obviously.
He'll collect the lords.
Tell us what you think, Osman Bey.
Togay went to see Nikola.
So, they are together in this.
He wants to attack us, Osman Bey.
We should attack them before they do.
Thank you, brother.
I think the same as you.
I want to kill the lords first.
How will we benefit from it, Osman Bey?
I'll start with Aris, Lord of Yarhisar,
who is the most difficult one.
I'll keep him here for sometime and...
spread rumors that we work together.
And Nikola will be left alone.
They will be afraid to work
together and...
we will defeat
the İnegöl Castle, Inshallah.
Inshallah.
What are we waiting for, father?
Let me deal with this.
It's our problem now.
We will figure this out without
Osman Bey knowing.
If he does things without telling us...
we'll do the same.
What are you thinking, father?
We're both harmed.
We'll ask for Togay.
Forgive me, my Bey...
but why does Nikola give us Togay?
Does he want to make Geyhatu angry?
Firstly, we'll send a messenger.
We'll tell him that if we take Togay, we
won't touch him.
If Osman Bey stands up to Lord Nikola...
then what can a Kızılbeyoğlu do?
If it's about going to İnegöl...
we will.
However, I see that he's
in trouble in the tent.
Go to İnegöl as a messenger.
- Your command, my Bey.
- Father.
I want to go if you let me.
They may do bad things, daughter.
If I am your heir, if you see me
worthy of this...
then let me go.
Bring Alaca with you.
Take some Alps with you.
However, be careful, okay?
It's yours.
So, he'll attack the Lord
of Yarhisar, huh?
Will you tell him?
I won't, Hatun.
Osman began to trust me.
I should be careful.
You won't just wait, right?
I have some plans, Hatun.
Thank you.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (Ithe name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.)
- No, thank you.
- Drink it.
It's healthy.
Thank you.
Abdurrahman Ghazi...
Davut Bey...
...welcome.
I'm so happy you're here.
It's us who are happy, my Sheikh.
If you have no one to talk to...
even if you talk like a canary, it's
in vain.
You go to wars and fight a lot.
Ahis start working by morning pray...
and try to gain money until dawn.
We just talk.
Not at all, my Sheikh.
Beys fight and...
Ahis talk about it.
What then?
There will be a conquest.
A conquest won't be complete
with just a sword.
Doesn't it mean opening?
Open where?
Open to who? From outside or inside?
The sword opens it from outside.
What will open it from inside?
Having Allah's calling.
The door of a wall is opened with a
sword.
What about the door of a heart?
How will it be opened?
Can someone be a Muslim with a sword
if he doesn't feel like a Muslim?
How can this happen?
Ahi will work, produce and sell.
Ahi will buy, make and do.
They shouldn't cheat while working.
Ahis will thrive what is
taken by the sword.
They will make it prosperous.
When serving the public means
serving to Allah...
then the conquest will be complete.
And Islam will spread in the state.
The state will be complete.
If we have summons from Allah, then
we will know that...
we will get our acts together.
We will be fair to Muslims and...
non- muslims.
If Hasan isn't fair to our neighbors
and everyone...
there won't be a state for us here.
If the blacksmith Davut Bey
can't do self-preservation...
there won't be a state for us here.
We won't be complete until we are fair.
According to some, mushriks from
Mecca were so cruel.
Their cruelty was so harsh that...
everyone was oppressed.
Our Efendi saw that the oppression...
was getting crueler every day...
and He had felt sad.
He decided something to...
rescue his companions.
And he sent the Muslims to
Najashi, King of Habesh.
Najashi was a Christian.
And our Efendi knew that
he was a Christian.
He said that...
"Go to Najashi, he is a fair King."
That's it.
Our Efendi...
didn't care about Najashi being
a Christian, Muslim or Jew.
He said he was fair.
There is no leader for us other
than our Efendi. (Muhammad.)
Then, we will follow our leader...
or we won't and we will be destroyed.
Someone is following us.
No. Stay still.
Now is not the time.
Alaca.
Hide us.
Take off your cloth.
We will go where we will meet alone.
Let's meet there when we get rid
of the man who follows us.
Alaca, be careful.
Let's fall apart.
Come on.
This is not good.
This is not good at all.
Alps!
From now on...
Our enemy isn't just one.
Our shields aren't strong as their tricks.
However, we will beat them...
with our minds...
not just with our swords.
We will be together.
We will be one and beat them
like an iron fist.
You...
are my fighter valiants behind me.
We won't feel pity for anyone today.
However, I want the lord alive.
The rest will be killed by your swords.
Alps, come on!
I'm here as the messenger
of my father Umur Bey.
What do you want from me, the
messenger of Umur Bey, Malhun Hatun?
I want Togay, Geyhatu's dog.
What will you...
give me in return for him?
Osman's head?
In return for it, you'll keep your head.
What if...
I don't give Togay?
My father and Osman Bey will
destroy your castle.
You should know that.
It seems you found each other.
Allah-u Akbar! (Allah is the most great!)
Protect the lord!
Don't lift your shields down.
Hold on.
Attack!
Allah-u Akbar! (Allah is the most great!)
Bring me the lord.
Tie him.
If you...
carry...
rice in the wrong way...
you will...
carry...
soil...
while you're going back.
Sir, Osman caught Lord Aris and
brought him to his tent.
Togay...
"I bear witness that there is
no deity but Allah..."
Togay, don't kill her.
She will give us Osman.
"...and I bear witness that Muhammad
is the messenger of Allah."
My lion! He brings victory every day!
Thank Allah.
- We're getting rid of black clouds.
- Thank Allah.
He brought the Lord of Yarhisar.
No one can stop him, Dündar Bey.
Bring him inside.
What happened?
My Bey...
Malhun Hatun and her Alps
disappeared without a trace.
The blood started to
drop from Osman's sword.
You can go, Boran.
Come.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (Ithe name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.)
Are you hungry? Eat.
Thank you.
Okay.
These meats are from our animals.
Bulghur...
came from Konya.
The plums in this sherbet
came from İzmir.
Kayı Tent and Söğüt are the centers
of all ways.
It's at the center of all trade ways...
from İznik to Anatolia in Constantine.
Now...
what percentage of a tax
is given to Nikola...
by a merchant
who wants to sell goods in İnegöl?
Two fifths.
Two fifths?
And he promised to protect
you from me in return for it?
Here I am.
In front of you.
You're in my tent.
You're sitting here.
Tell me.
Is it necessary to protect you from me?
Is it?
Do you know why you are here?
If...
you give up on your
collaboration with Nikola...
I will forgive your life.
And we will make a new trade agreement
for our friendship.
My hostility brings death...
and my friendship brings benefit.
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come in.
You should have a look, my Bey.
Togay.
Osman.
Look...
I'm alone.
Are you here to die?
Death only comes when I summon it.
Alps.
Be careful. Send some Alps around
the tent.
It might be a trap.
Come on.
I have his daughter.
If you want her to
live, give the Lord to me.
If you harm her...
I will cut your bones off...
and hang your skin on the entrance of the
tent.
If you want Umur's daughter...
bring your prisoner to Karaçayır...
as long as I'm here, Osman Bey.
As long as Togay lives...
his daughter lives too.
We once worshipped the same sky...
with your generation, Osman Bey.
The sky we worshipped is split.
Now, our ways are
separated from each other.
Only blood can clear those ways.
When the time comes, we will continue
what our fathers have left unfinished.
You kidnap women...
like your father.
I won't continue doing anything with
an ignoble like you.
I...
will cut you off under this blue sky.
A good enemy is here.
Bring the lord.
If you make me wait here for long...
you will hang her head as an ornament on
your tent.
Can I...
go now?
Alps!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com